Warning! The footage you are about to watch is of a sensitive nature
and although it may not be suitable for all viewers, it is for the glory of God.
Jesus said in the Book of Matthew 11:28, "Come to me all of you who are weary
and carry heavy burdens and I will give you rest".
At the Synagogue Church Of All Nations, this gentleman carries a small boy in his arms.
Due to the severity of his problem, he cannot walk or even stand on his own
because of the excruciating pain of the hot water burns he sustained in a terrible accident.
The hot water burns scorched from the top of his thigh all the way down his leg.
He is not able to wear his trousers
as any contact with the burns will cause extreme pain and discomfort for this young boy.
The boy's skin glistens with puss and blood, and it's raw and incredibly painful.
A burn of this degree would defy any medical solution.
They have come to the Synagogue Church Of All Nations believing
that Jesus Christ can put an end to this young boy's suffering.
Please tell us your name, your age and your address.
My name is Mr Tairu. The boy sitting on my lap is the son of my brother.
What's his name and age?
His name is Master Jelili Tairu and he is twelve years old.
Can you tell us the problem that brought this little boy to the Synagogue Church Of All Nations today?
The problem that brought us here is hot water burns.
You mean he has hot water burns?
Yes
Since this problem started, he cannot walk or eat. He is in pain and agony.
That is what we have been facing from when it started until this time.
Can you tell us who has been assisting him to go about doing all these things?
His mother and I.
His mother and you?
Yes.
Can you tell us when and where you have taken him to for solution before coming to The SCOAN?
We took him to the hospital.
The doctor tried all efforts but there was no improvement.
The doctor himself told me about The SCOAN.
After he made all efforts, he told me to bring the boy to The SCOAN,
so that he would come and receive his healing.
You mean the doctor who had been treating this boy directed you to The SCOAN
so that this boy could be set free through God's intervention?
Yes, sir.
Ok. What is your belief in God today?
I believe in God that Jesus Christ will set us free today.
I pray with you that God Almighty will set this brother free
from this problem of hot water burns today, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
This traumatising experience is too much for twelve-year-old Master Jelili Taitu.
A young boy should not have to suffer this kind of torment and affliction.
But despite the unbearable pain, he waits in faith believing that by Jesus' stripes,
his healing has been paid for and provided freely.
HEALING TIME
This is Master Jelili Tairu, harldy able to sit on his uncle's lap at The SCOAN prayer line
because of the sensitivity of the terrible wound caused by the hot water burns.
Prophet T.B. Joshua stretches forth his hand in the name of Jesus Christ
to declare peace, comfort and freedom to this young boy's body, soul and spirit.
As visitors from all over the world watch and are amazed at the horrendous suffering
that this boy has gone through,
the man of God continues to be used as a channel of healing in the young boy's life.
Declared free, the young boy is able to rise to his feet and walk all by himself.
Thirteen years later, Mr Jelili Tairu came back to The SCOAN
to testify to the healing power in the name of Jesus Christ.
Before and After
To God be the glory!
On the right hand side of the screen, you can see Jelili Tairu's leg
has been miraculously healed from the hot water burns he had suffered from when he was a small boy.
On the left is a reminder of the terrible wound that once covered this young man's leg.
A wound of this severity goes beyond medical science and doctors.
What wasn't possible for men was possible for God.
Indeed, Jesus Christ is the Master Healer.
When Jesus Christ heals, he heals completely; he heals effectually.
The skin on Mr Jelili Tairu's leg has been completely restored back to the original position
in which God had created it.
Before and After
Please tell us your name and where you are from.
My name is Jelili Tairu.
Since the prayer of the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, I have been healed.
I have no more pain on my legs. Everything is gone.
I really thank and appreciate God.
Hallelujah. So can we see you tap the area?
As you are tapping and rubbing it now, are you feeling any pain?
No, I'm not feeling any pain.
Can you wear trousers and do all the things you normally did before now?
Before, when I had the burns on my legs, I could not wear jeans, trousers or even short knickers.
I hardly wore trousers; I only wore pants and boxers.
But now after the prayer of the man of God, what can you do?
After the prayer of the man of God, I felt very strong.
I am able to wear trousers.
I feel okay; I no longer have pain on my legs.
I am feeling well.
Can you wear your trousers now? Let's see it.
So tell us - are you feeling any pain and discomfort as your are dressing up now?
No, I don't feel pain; I feel fine now.
Glory be to God. Once again, can you tap that area and show us that you're not feeling any pain there?
Mr Jelili Tairu's leg has been completely restored and is completely free from the hot water burns.
Thank You, Jesus!
Thank You, Jesus, for healing me and saving my life!
TESTIMONY TIME
So right now, brother, can you tell us your name and your testimony.
My name is Tairu Jelili.
I am here to share the goodness of God in my life.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN was hot water burns.
It happened one day when my mother was boiling water in the kitchen.
She sent me to the kitchen to check if the water was boiling.
After getting to the kitchen, I checked the water
and the pot of water fell and poured on my thigh down to my foot.
So I screamed .
My mother heard my voice and rushed into the kitchen.
After rushing into the kitchen, she found me lying on the floor crying and moaning.
She called some neighbours who helped her take me to the hospital.
For several months I received treatment but there was no change.
My uncle heard that I was sick.
He was told that I was sick, so he came and checked on me.
When he came to my place where I lived with my mum,
he discovered that I was very sick; I was lying in bed.
He told my mum about The SCOAN.
My mother accepted and he brought me to The SCOAN.
He brought me to The SCOAN and I was taken to the prayer line
and that was where I received my healing.
As soon as the man of God, Prophet T.B.Joshua prayed for me,
I began to feel a cold sensation within me.
What I was not able to do before, I was able to do it.
For several months, I had been at home, unable to walk on my own.
I couldn't take my bath or do anything on my own because the pain was too much.
On that fateful day, I was able to walk; I was so surprised.
As soon as the man of God prayed for me, I began to walk.
I was surprised.
I appreciate God for what He has done in my life.
Thank You, Jesus, for saving me!
For how long have you been healed?
I have been healed for over 13 years.
And now, how are you feeling right now?
I am feeling strong as you can see.
There is no pain; I no longer feel pain on my leg.
So you can tap the leg right now?
Yes, I can tap it. I no longer feel any pain.
Could you wear trousers like these then?
Before, I was not able to wear trousers; I would only wear underpants.
Even the underpants were difficult for me to wear.
But now I am free. I can wear trousers.
I can wear whatever I want.
I am okay; I am strong.
Mr Jelili Tairu - Healed of Hot Water Burns
So can you show yourself round to the people.
I would like to tell you that you should have faith in God.
There is nothing God cannot do.
You can see what God has done for me in my life.
Before, I was told in the hospital that my leg would be stiff,
that I would have been walking like this.
But now, God used Prophet T.B. Joshua to pray for me and now, I am healed.
As you can see, my leg is straight.
I can walk now.
I no longer feel pain on my leg, as if there were no hot water burns.
You should have faith in God; there is nothing God cannot do.
As soon as God uses Prophet T.B. Joshua to pray for you, don't go into sin again.
Have faith in God. That's all I have to say.
Thank you.
Let's give a round of applause for our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ!
Mr Jelili Tairu - Healed of Hot Water Burns
Right now, we are encouraging you to walk in the light of your testimony
by staying closer to Jesus Christ because He has healed you to follow Him
and not to stay where you are.
So we pray with you that God Almighty will continue to
uphold you to press on in His way and in His Truth, in Jesus Christ's name.
Amen!